Guide to President's Office (Richard M. Turner) Records 1972-1990
Lane Community College
- Internal Organizations - College Departments, Committees, and Subject Files, 1971-1990; 13.2 cubic feet, 33 document boxes
  - Telecommunications Task Force, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 42/3)
  - Telephone Registration Task Force, 1986 (Box-folder 42/4)
  - Torch, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 42/5)
  - Training Program Policy, 1987 (Box-folder 42/6)
  - Travel, 1987 (Box-folder 42/7)
  - Tuition, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 42/8)
  - Tuition Waivers, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 42/9)
  - Union Matters, 1987 (Box-folder 42/10)
  - U.S. Government, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 42/11)
  - U.S. Representatives, 1987 (Box-folder 42/12)
  - U. S. Senators (Mark Hatfield, Bob Packwood), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 42/13)
  - Veterans Administration, 1986 (Box-folder 42/14)
  - Vision Statements, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 42/15)
  - Vocational Education, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 42/16-21)
  - Vocational Education Advisory Committee, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 43/1)
  - Vocational Education Consortium, 1987 (Box-folder 43/2)
  - Warford, Larry, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 43/3)
  - Welfare Reform Task Force, 1988 (Box-folder 43/4)
  - Wellness Task Force, 1988 (Box-folder 43/5)
  - Women’s Program, 1987 (Box-folder 43/6)
  - Women’s Studies, Barry, Kate, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 43/7)
  - Women’s Studies Program, 1982 (Box-folder 43/8)
  - Word Processing, 1986 (Box-folder 43/9)
  - Work Activity Center, 1986 (Box-folder 43/10)
  - Work Force, 1987 (Box-folder 43/11-12)
  - Work Load, 1987 (Box-folder 43/13)
  - Miscellaneous, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 43/14)
- External Organizations, 1973-1989; 6.4 cubic feet, 16 document boxes
  This contains files relating to organizations outside of the college. These are regional organizations such as local chambers of commerce, other community colleges in Oregon, Oregon state educational agencies, Oregon community college organizations, and national organizations, such as the League for Innovation in the Community College.
  - American Association for Higher Education, 1987 (Box-folder 44/1)
  - American Association of Community and Junior Colleges (AACJC), 1986-1988 (Box-folder 44/2-4)
  - American College Testing Program, 1987 (Box-folder 44/5)
  - American Council on Education, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 44/6-7)
  - American Express, 1988 (Box-folder 44/8)
  - Association of Community College Trustees (ACCT), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 44/9-10)
  - Blue Mountain Community College, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 44/11)
  - Boy Scouts of America, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 44/12)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1987 (Box-folder 44/13)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Cottage Grove, 1988 (Box-folder 44/14)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Eugene, 1988 (Box-folder 44/15-16)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Florence, 1988 (Box-folder 44/17)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Springfield, 1988 (Box-folder 44/18)
  - Chemeketa Community College, 1987 (Box-folder 45/1)
  - Clakamas Community College, 1987 (Box-folder 45/2)
  - Colleges, 1988 (Box-folder 45/3)
  - Community College Services, 1987 (Box-folder 45/4-5)
  - Community Colleges, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 45/6-7)
  - Construction Assistance Plan, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 45/8-10)
  - Cooperative Work Experience, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 45/11-12)
  - Digital Equipment Corporation, Computer Software, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 45/13)
  - Ed-Net, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 45/14, 46/1-2)
  - El-Jay, Inc, 1987 (Box-folder 46/3)
  - Equity Task Force, 1988 (Box-folder 62/1)
  - Eugene, City of, 1988 (Box-folder 46/4)
  - Eugene Metropolitan Rotary Club, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 63/5)
  - Eugene Public Library, 1988 (Box-folder 46/5)
  - Eugene/Springfield Convention, 1987 (Box-folder 46/6)
  - Eugene/Springfield Metropolitan Partnership, 1988 (Box-folder 46/7)
  - Family Employment Program, 1987 (Box-folder 46/8)
  - IBM, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 46/9)
  - Lane Council of Governments (L-COG), 1988 (Box-folder 46/10)
  - Lane County, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 46/11-12)
  - Lane County Fair, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 46/13-15)
  - Lane County Schools, 1988 (Box-folder 46/16-17)
  - Lane Educational Service District (ESD), 1988 (Box-folder 47/1)
  - League for Innovation, American Interactive Media, 1987 (Box-folder 48/2)
  - League for Innovation, Community College and the Computer, 1985 (Box-folder 48/3)
  - League for Innovation, Conference (LCC Host), 1986 (Box-folder 48/4)
  - League for Innovation, Conferences and Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 48/5-9)
  - League for Innovation, Correspondence, 1973-1989 (Box-folder 47/2-11)
  - League for Innovation, General, 1969-1987 (Box-folder 48/1)
  - League for Innovation, Innovator of the Year, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 48/10-12)
  - League for Innovation, National Advisory Committee on the Computer, 1987 (Box-folder 48/13)
  - League for Innovation, Organizational Charts, 1988 (Box-folder 48/14)
  - League for Innovation, Student Services, 1986 (Box-folder 48/15)
  - League for Innovation, Telecommunications Workshop, 1985 (Box-folder 48/16)
  - League for Innovation, Visit, 1985 (Box-folder 48/17)
  - Linn-Benton Community College, 1987 (Box-folder 48/18)
  - Lions Club, 1988 (Box-folder 48/19)
  - Mills and Associates, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 48/20)
  - Ministerial Association, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 49/1)
  - Mt. Hood Community College, 1987 (Box-folder 49/1)
  - National Association of College and University Business Officers (NACUBO), 1987 (Box-folder 49/3)
  - National Commission for Cooperative Education (NCCE), 1985-1988 (Box-folder 49/4-5)
  - National Community Education Association (NCEA), 1986 (Box-folder 49/6)
  - National Institute for Staff and Organizational Development (NISOD), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 49/7-8)
  - Northwest Association of Schools and Colleges, 1988 (Box-folder 49/9)
  - Office of Education Policy and Planning, 1988 (Box-folder 62/2)
  - Oregon Career Information System, 1988 (Box-folder 49/10)
  - Oregon Community College Association (OCCA), Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 49/11-16, 50/1-2)
  - OCCA, Conferences and Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 50/3-4)
  - OCCA, Legislative Initiatives, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 50/5-6)
  - OCCA, Administrative Salary Surveys, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 50/7-8)
  - OCCA, Faculty Salary Surveys, 1973-1989 (Box-folder 50/9-11)
  - OCCA, Workshop, 1988 (Box-folder 50/12-13)
  - Oregon Community College Presidents Council, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 51/1-8)
  - Oregon Community College Telecommunications Consortium, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 51/9, 62/3)
  - Oregon Community Education Association, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 51/10, 62/4)
  - Oregon Department of Education, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 51/11-14, 52/1-7, 62/5)
  - Oregon Department of Education, Vocational Educational Plan, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 52/8)
  - Oregon Economic Development, 1987 (Box-folder 52/9)
  - Oregon Governor’s Office, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 52/10-12)
  - Oregon Legislature, 1987 (Box-folder 53/1)
  - Oregon Museum Park, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 53/2-4)
  - Oregon Private Industry Council Consortium, 1988 (Box-folder 62/6)
  - Oregon School Boards Association, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 53/5, 62/7)
  - Oregon Small Business Development Center Network (OSBDCN), 1984-1988 (Box-folder 53/6-14, 62/8)
  - OSBDCN, Reports, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 54/1-4)
  - Oregon State Agencies (various), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 54/5)
  - Oregon State Board of Education, 1988 (Box-folder 54/6-9, 62/10)
  - Oregon State System of Higher Education, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 54/10, 62/11)
  - Oregon State System of Higher Education, Semester Conversion, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 55/1)
  - Oregon State University, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 55/2-3)
  - Portland Community College, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 55/4)
  - Phi Theta Kappa, 1987 (Box-folder 55/5)
  - Phi Beta Lambda, 1987 (Box-folder 55/6)
  - Riverfront Research Park, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 55/7-9)
  - Rogue Community College, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 55/10)
  - Southern Willamette Private Industry Council (SWPIC), 1985-1988 (Box-folder 55/11-15, 63/1-2)
  - Southern Willamette Research Corridor, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 56/1-4, 63/3)
  - Southwestern Oregon Community College, 1987 (Box-folder 56/5)
  - Springfield, City of, 1988 (Box-folder 56/6)
  - Springfield Urban Renewal Plan, 1987 (Box-folder 56/7)
  - Tillamook Bay Community College, 1987 (Box-folder 56/8)
  - Treasure Valley Community College, 1987 (Box-folder 56/9)
  - Treaty Oak Community College, 1986 (Box-folder 56/10)
  - U.S. Congress, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 56/11)
  - U.S. Department of Education, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 56/12-13)
  - U.S. Senate, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 56/14)
  - United Way, 1987 (Box-folder 56/15)
  - University of Oregon, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 56/16-17)
  - University of Oregon, Center for Educational Policy Management, Salary Survey, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 56/18)
  - Universities and Colleges (various), 1988 (Box-folder 56/19)
  - VISA Credit Cards, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 57/1)
  - Watson and Associates, 1987 (Box-folder 57/2)
  - Willamette Valley Racial Minorities Consortium, 1985 (Box-folder 57/3)
  - Wisner Associates, 1986 (Box-folder 57/4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 57/5)
- Speeches and Writings, 1982-1988; .8 cubic feet, 2 document boxes
  This series contains Turner’s speeches and writings.
  - Speeches and Writings, 1982-1988 (Box-folder 57/6-58/6)
- Legal Records, 1983-1989; 1.2 cubic feet, 3 document boxes
  This contains legal records which are retained for historical interest. The series contains records concerning ASHLane (a case involving student housing) and financial aid and Adult Basic and Secondary Education personnel issues.
  Because these records may contain employee personnel records, they are confidential and access is restricted.
  - Legal Records, A-Z, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 59-61)